<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Speakers on South Dakota Code Camp</title>
    <link>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Speakers on South Dakota Code Camp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:40:03 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jackson Murtha</title>
      <link>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/jackson-murtha/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 11:53:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/jackson-murtha/</guid>
      <description>Jackson Murtha is Systems Architect at Blend Interactive in Sioux Falls. He does web development, Linux things, and &amp;ldquo;DevOps&amp;rdquo; work. He&amp;rsquo;s also interested in obscure nerdy things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Jacobson</title>
      <link>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/robert-jacobson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 16:06:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/robert-jacobson/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a Software Engineer with Raven Industries working on connected solutions and infrastructure. Shortly after the initial release of Docker I started working to &amp;ldquo;containerize all the things.&amp;rdquo; Outside of work I can commonly be found gaming with my wife, cycling, at the gym, or working on &amp;ldquo;this month&amp;rsquo;s inspiration.&amp;rdquo; (http://www.commitstrip.com/en/2014/11/25/west-side-project-story/)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Bushee</title>
      <link>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/will-bushee/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 10:23:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/will-bushee/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m an avid technology enthusiast and a firm believer that almost any problem can be solved with a little creative thinking, the proper dataset, or by building the correct enrichment of web data. I enjoy working with kids, entrepreneurs, early-stage startups, and those struggling with the latest technology.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bob Davidson</title>
      <link>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/bob-davidson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 10:04:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/bob-davidson/</guid>
      <description>I am a Web Developer of various disciplines, focusing primarily on C# / ASP.NET. I spend most of my time working on CMS-based websites, though work occasionally in NodeJS/Livescript, PHP, and if pressed, Coldfusion. I&amp;rsquo;m a fan of Episerver, have a minor fascination with monadic parsers, and am still getting the hang of F#.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Him Acharya</title>
      <link>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/him-acharya/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 09:35:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/him-acharya/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Him Acharya is a Development Manager at CHR Solutions in Sioux Falls where he owns the development team for one of the core product. He has been in the software industry for more than 10 years and is always open to learn new techs and share it with others. His past work involved graduate programmer, software developer, Development lead and now the dev manager.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logan Drews</title>
      <link>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/logan-drews/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 09:11:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/logan-drews/</guid>
      <description>Logan Drews is a Senior Software Engineer at CHR Solutions in Sioux Falls, South Dakota and works to provide the scaling and features for ever-growing telecommunication companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joel Kauffman</title>
      <link>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/joel-kauffman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 10:55:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/joel-kauffman/</guid>
      <description>Joel Kauffman is the lead developer for Worthington Ag Parts in Sioux Falls, SD. Joel has spoken previously at various conferences in the region, and enjoys meeting and talking with people who share his passion for technology. When he isn’t speaking or building software, Joel spends time with his wife and 4 kids, and is remodeling his 1886 house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miles Rausch</title>
      <link>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/miles-rausch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 10:18:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/miles-rausch/</guid>
      <description>Miles Rausch is a web developer from Sioux Falls, South Dakota. He&amp;rsquo;s a writer for people and a writer for computers. He seems destined to spend time at a keyboard. Miles currently works at Carsforsale.com where he does full-stack development on the flagship product, Carsforsale.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Boedigheimer</title>
      <link>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/robert-boedigheimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 16:17:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/robert-boedigheimer/</guid>
      <description>Robert Boedigheimer works for Schwans Shared Services, LLC providing business solutions with web technologies. Robert has been developing web sites for the past 20 years. He is an ASP.NET MVP, a Pluralsight author, and a 3rd degree black belt in Tae Kwon Do. Robert regularly speaks at national and international events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kris Boedigheimer</title>
      <link>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/kris-boedigheimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 16:13:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/kris-boedigheimer/</guid>
      <description>I am a former computer programmer turned homeschool mom who loves learning, travel, exercise, reading, finding exciting new hobbies, and spending time with family. My favorite subjects are programming, math, and logic. Besides teaching homeschool I am a third degree black belt in Tae Kwon Do, Advanced Level Toastmaster Speaker, and group fitness instructor for Les Mills Bodyflow, and Les Milles BodyAttack. We travel constantly and make it a habit to try something different at each location including blown glass, painting classes, surfing, carving carousel animals, and trapeze class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Logan</title>
      <link>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/kevin-logan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 14:43:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://southdakotacodecamp.com/speakers/kevin-logan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been a developer for over 12 years at Omnitech and have worked on a variety of .Net projects. I work mostly in .Net with a focus on UI development in web applications, but lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been working with Service Fabric.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>